{"test_questions": [[{"question": "The fact that the same operation may apply to two or more classes is called what?", "opta": "Inheritance", "optb": "Polymorphism", "optc": "Encapsulation", "optd": "Multiple classification", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The object-oriented development life cycle is which of the following?", "opta": "Analysis, design, and implementation steps in the given order and using multiple iterations.", "optb": "Analysis, design, and implementation steps in the given order and going through the steps no more than one time.", "optc": "Analysis, design, and implementation steps in any order and using multiple iterations.", "optd": "Analysis, design, and implementation steps in any order and going through the steps no more than one time.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Multiplicity is the same as what concept for an ERD?", "opta": "Relationship", "optb": "Attribute", "optc": "Entity", "optd": "Cardinality", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Composition is a stronger form of which of the following?", "opta": "Aggregation", "optb": "Encapsulation", "optc": "Inheritance", "optd": "All of the above.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "An abstract class is which of the following?", "opta": "A class that has direct instances, but whose descendants may have direct instances.", "optb": "A class that has no direct instances, but whose descendants may have direct instances.", "optc": "A class that has direct instances, but whose descendants may not have direct instances.", "optd": "A class that has no direct instances, but whose descendants may not have direct instances", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The term Complete for a UML has the same meaning as which of the following for an EER diagram?", "opta": "Overlapping rule", "optb": "Disjoint rule", "optc": "Total specialization rule", "optd": "Partial specialization rule", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A UML diagram includes which of the following?", "opta": "Class name", "optb": "List of attributes", "optc": "List of operations", "optd": "All of the above.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "An object can have which of the following multiplicities?", "opta": "Zero", "optb": "One", "optc": "More than one", "optd": "All of the above.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following statement is true concerning objects and/or classes?", "opta": "An object is an instance of a class.", "optb": "A class is an instance of an object.", "optc": "An object includes encapsulates only data.", "optd": "A class includes encapsulates only data.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following applies to a class rather than an object?", "opta": "Query", "optb": "Update", "optc": "Scope", "optd": "Constructor", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The benefits of object-oriented modeling are which of the following?", "opta": "The ability to tackle more challenging problems", "optb": "Reusability of analysis, design, and programming results", "optc": "Improved communication between users, analysts, etc.", "optd": "All of the above.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The term Incomplete for a UML has the same meaning as which of the following for an EER diagram?", "opta": "Overlapping rule", "optb": "Disjoint rule", "optc": "Total specialization rule", "optd": "Partial specialization rule", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A constructor operation does which of the following?", "opta": "Creates a new instance of a class", "optb": "Updates an existing instance of a class", "optc": "Deletes and existing instance of a class", "optd": "All of the above.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following is a technique for hiding the internal implementation details of an object?", "opta": "Encapsulation", "optb": "Polymorphism", "optc": "Inheritance", "optd": "All of the above.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Aggregation is which of the following?", "opta": "Expresses a part-of relationship and is a stronger form of an association relationship.", "optb": "Expresses a part-of relationship and is a weaker form of an association relationship.", "optc": "Expresses an is-a relationship and is a stronger form of an association relationship.", "optd": "Expresses an is-a relationship and is a weaker form of an association relationship.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}